It's about time.
We're still looking for
a place to find a place.
We're still looking for a time.
We're not going to be
able to fight the fight.
We're not
going to be
able to fight the fight.
RAAAAAAH!
Hmm? Huh?
Hey, do you hear that noise too?
They've arrived.
It's a helicopter!
Thanks for the update, Captain Obvious.
They're here from the
Speedwagon Foundation,
and they're looking for somewhere to land.
Speed Wagon Foundation?
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but aren't they the group that's
looking after Mom back in Japan?
They're old friends of yours, right?
Yep, that's them, all right.
So what?
Are we taking a helicopter
from here on out?
Not quite.
As much as I'd like to, the guys working
for the Foundation aren't stand users,!
so we'd be putting them in
harm's way if we hitched a ride.
Well, if they're not here to give us
a ride, what's the occasion, then?
They brought us our new ally.
Huh?
Turigol? An ally?
I have to warn you,
he's a bit of a handful,
which is the primary reason
it took so long to fetch him.
Mr.
Joestar, you aren't seriously
considering taking him with us, are you?
His presence here would only hold us back.
So he might actually harm us? Correct.
So be careful.
Not so fast.
This new ally of ours, are you
saying that he's a stand user too?
Yes, that's right, and his stand is
represented by the card known as the Fool.
The fool?
Wait, the fool? Ha ha!
Ha ha!
Sounds like a pretty stupid
card if you want my opinion.
You should count your blessings
that he's on our side.
You can't beat him.
I'd suggest watching your mouth if
you know what's good for you, Avdol.
It's true, Polnareff.
Now move your hand.
You're hurting me.
Who died and made you the boss?
Enough, you two.
The helicopter's here.
Mr.
Joestar, good to see you.
Thank you for bringing him here.
Must have been rough.
So, which one of you is it?
Who's the stand user?
Well you're gonna answer
me or not is it you no
sir neither of us is the
user he's actually in the
back in the
back huh I
don't see anyone no he's
there hey hey cut it out
come on quit Joking around.
What's the deal, is the guy
really short or something?
Come out, come out, wherever you are!
Hey, watch out!
Huh?
That's weird, what the hell is this stuff?
Please be careful, it was a rough
copter ride so he's in a foul mood.
Step away, I've already told
you this guy is trouble.
Get back Polnareff, you cannot beat him.
What's the big deal?
All I'm doing is asking where he is.
A dog!
Don't tell me this dog is...
Yes, this dog possesses
the stand of the fool.
His name is Iggy, and he's crazy about
ripping chunks of hair out of people's heads.
To be honest with you, I'm
not sure where he's from,
but Avdol found him in New York after none
of the dog catchers could wrangle him.
And it's thanks to Avdol that
he's not roaming the streets now.
Oh, there's something that I
probably should have mentioned.
When he's in the middle of
ripping out someone's hair,
he likes to, uh, pass gas in their face.
It's a disgusting habit, really.
You little mutt!
You're gonna pay for that!
Damn you!
Tarion!
Holy cow!
So that thing is the fool.
When we were in Singapore, we fought
an orangutan stand user, but this is...
Who does this stupid mutt
think he is? Bastard!
Don't make me turn you into dog meat!
What the hell?
It turned into sand!
I can't cut him!
Damn it!
His stand is solidified and
grabbed hold of my rapier! Is that?
Yes, the dog's stand is
made entirely out of sand.
Hmm, as simple as the design is, it's so
powerful I'm not sure I could land a punch.
Guys, what are you doing? Help!
Get this dog off of me!
I'm sorry, Polnareff, but if it's all the
same to you, I'd like to keep my hand.
Monster!
Did you happen to bring his
favorite snack with you?
Of course I did.
He wouldn't have come with us otherwise.
Oh, my God, stop!
Help me!
The dog's sense of smell is
simply incredible. And that is?
It's coffee-flavored chewing gum,
and iggy will do just about anything!
to savor this tasty little morsel. No! Mr.
Avdol, quickly, hide
the packet before you...
Blast it!
He grabbed the whole thing!
He can't get enough of his
coffee-flavored gum, as you can see.
People, on the other hand, are a
different story, unfortunately.
The least he can do is
take the wrapping off.
How is a gum-obsessed feral
dog supposed to help us?
Damn that little menace!
He's completely ruined
my picturesque hair!
Partied corn!
He'll be distracted while
he's chewing his gum.
Let's get the supplies.
Here's the food and water you'll
be needing for your trip, sir.
Oh, thank you.
There are medical supplies
and a change of clothes, too.
We also took the liberty of buying
a new camera to use with your stand.
Yeah, I suppose it'll be a lot
easier than using a TV, right?
Oh, I know.
Look sharp, Ben.
Fantastic.
This is a perfect memento.
Eftel, hurry up and give
the mutt the stupid cum!
Now why in the world would I do that,
when the two of you are already
such good friends, Folder F?
Well, if that's everything, I think
we're going to be heading back now, Mr.
Joestar.
Answer this before you leave.
It's regarding my daughter's condition.
And I want you to be straight with me.
How's my baby girl holding up?
Well to be perfectly frank with you
sir it's not looking good right now.
She's rapidly losing strength and
nothing seems to help her condition.
Our doctors at the Speedwagon Foundation
say she has two weeks at best.
We're all out of time this is bullshit.
I also have some other information sir.
Our investigators say that two days ago,
nine unidentified men and women gathered
in a building believed to be Dio's hideout.
Apparently, they came and left together.
Dio has rounded up nine more people?
We have no clue who they are.
The spy who reported this
was killed shortly after,
and the mansion where
they met has been vacated.
We've had no luck in
locating these individuals.
We thought about tailing them,
but since our spies aren't stand users,
we decided it would be too dangerous.
So these people are stand users? Hold on.
Think about it for a minute.
That would be impossible.
Other than whole horses stand the Emperor,
the only tarot card that
still remains is the world.
I've been suspecting that one
belongs to Dio, but now I'm not sure.
Avdol? I...
I don't know.
I just can't wrap my head around this.
Nine more stand users?
From what I can gather,
it seems that Dio's head hasn't been
able to adjust to his new body yet.
But that monster would never run from us.
He's far too conceited
for something like that.
He'll do everything within his
power to keep us out of Cairo.
Good freaking grief.
We have to take out nine
stand users in two weeks, huh?
Man, that is one hell of a whirlwind tour.
Have a safe trip, Mr. Joestar.
We await your return.
Thanks for your help.
Look after my holly!
That mutt.
So, it sniffed out the great
Endul from that far away?
So close.
What do you know?
I almost caught it this time.
Just a bit more practice, all of
this because of the tsetse fly.
If not for those insects,
Joe Starr and his band of meddlers would
never have known Master Dio was in Egypt.
Mr.
Joestar, why are you letting
him get away with this?
It's not Farragus to be in the backseat
while we're stuck in the trunk.
And in case you didn't know, it's
not exactly spacious back here.
I'm gonna need a chiropractor!
Look, I know it's not ideal,
but you'll just have to wait
until the gum runs out of flavor.
When it does, throw another stick of gum
into the trunk to lure him back there.
Then you can all switch seats with
all right all right calm down already
fleabag damn
you're annoying whoa
what the hell was that hey quickly
look over there there do you see
it it's the helicopter the speed
wagon foundation helicopter went
down i can't believe what i'm seeing.
There's no sign of an
explosion or gunfire.
It seems like it just fell out
of the sky for no reason at all.
Could it be? Careful, men.
I bet my life it was
attacked by an enemy's stand.
Over there.
It's the pilot.
He's already dead.
No.
Whatever happened to
him, it wasn't pretty.
The poor bastard.
Approach carefully.
Finally, whatever did this
could still be hiding in there.
It's water.
There's no way all that
water is just from his mouth.
It must be flowing from somewhere else.
It must be from his lungs.
And the fish would mean...
He drowned in the desert!
This is getting weirder and weirder!
What is going on? Hey!
We found the other guy
over here! He's alive!
Hang on!
You have to talk to us!
Tell us what happened!
Water...
What?
Are you saying you need water?
Hurry, Polnareff, hand me the canteen.
Huh? Oh, yeah.
Here, you just hang in there.
Drink this.
Drink it slowly.
No!
The water attacked us!
Man, watch yourselves. It's a stand.
The enemy's stand is inside the canteen!
Damn it all!
They were just innocent bystanders.
What reason did it have to kill them?
Avdol, did you see what kind
of stand we're dealing with?
I just saw the shape of a hand, but I'd
wager it's still inside the canteen.
I don't believe I saw it leave.
Who could the user be?
The Foundation members informed us Dio
had a meeting with nine men and women.
Is it possible that one
of them is the assassin?
Hey, I need you to find the
stand user. Yeah, I know.
I'm already on it. That said.
I don't see anything around
us, let alone the stand user.
When we duked it out with that sun
stand, he was hiding behind a mirror.
But this time,
the enemy seems to be so far away that
we'll never be able to find him from here.
Polnareff, slice up
the canteen, would you?
Why me?
Besides, didn't you see
what happened to the pilot?
His entire head got sucked into
that tiny little container.
Think about it.
If I so much as poke a
hole in that thing...
No way.
Why don't you slice it up, Kakyoin?
You're closer anyhow.
You can just use your emerald
splash and call it a day.
Can't you?
Yes, but I don't want to
Don't make me do something just
because you don't want to do it.
What the hell man?
What's going on with you?
I've said no and that's final.
Well, like I said, I'm not gonna
attack the damn thing either
That's the
K-Kakuin!
It's the water!
The stand left the canteen disguised
as water and hid in the blood!
No, that's wrong!
The stand wasn't disguising
itself as water at all!
I think the stand is the water! No!
It got Kakuin!
It closed up Kakuin's eyes!
Polnareff, panicking isn't
going to help anything!
Summon Chariot for protection!
Damn it, it'll get Polnareff too.
This doesn't make any sense.
Why would it go after the pilot's corpse?
It wasn't the corpse.
The target was the watch.
It attacked the watch
because of the alarm.
That's it!
The stand stalks its victims
by sound! You're kidding!
Get out of there, Polaramp!
It's coming after you now!
Hurry and get to the car!
It's so fast!
Faster, pull the raft!
It got me!
Hermit Purple!
The stand disappeared into the ground.
I see now.
It detects sound through
vibrations in the ground.
And it moves through the Earth,
so there's no way to find it.
That puts us at a major disadvantage.
Since we can't see it,
the Stand has the ability to attack from
above or below at any moment it chooses.
To make things worse, the Stand
user could be kilometers away.
So the Prey has sought
refuge atop the car.
Seems they've realized Until is using the
power of sound to hunt
them down one by one.
No matter.
It won't be long before
they're all eliminated.
Hey, how's Kakyoin doing? Not good.
From the looks of things,
he may have been blinded.
We have to get going.
He needs to see a doctor
as soon as possible.
But if we try to move from this
spot that stand will attack us?
We can't afford careless mistakes!
What the hell!
That sound it's the dog interesting it
leapt out of the car before i could attack!
It anticipated what my
stand was going to do
seems like this dog is
going to be quite the!
Nuisance the tires are
in the water shit what
now the whole car's about to be pulled in!
I can't hold him for long!
Everyone we have to move to the back!
Hey you good for nothing mongrel!
Aren't you supposed to be
helping us or something!
I see that a cursed dog is!
Too perceptive for his own good it knows
I'm four kilometers west of Joestar's!
Group
what to do?
Perhaps I should do away
with the dog right now.
Yes, leave while we fight to survive!
You're a bastard, you know that?
Never mind, the dog is of no concern.
Joestar and the others can't
control that mongrel anyway.
The mutt's harmless if all it does is nap.
Now for the kill!
Son of a bitch!
The water's sharp enough to
slash through our front tires!
Move to the other side on the double!
If it's trying to do what I think it is,
then we're gonna need to
hang on for our lives!
Thank you.
You can smell it, can't you?
You know where it's gonna
be before it gets there.
The stand's going after Jotaro!
If we can find whoever's
controlling the stand,
we might actually have a
chance of defeating him!
I saw a sticky idea.